[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas：RQ中有四种类型的函数，如果您能够管理
&gt;&gt; Douglas: RQ has four types of functions in it and if you can manage
这四种类型的函数，那么它就很容易使用了。
these four types of functions then it's it's pretty easy to use.
我们有请求者函数，这些函数可以执行请求。
We have requestor functions, which are functions that can execute a request.
我们有回调，它们是传递给
We've got callbacks, which are continuation functions that are passed to
请求者这就是请求者返回其结果的方式。
requestors that's how requester returns its result.
我们有工厂，就像你一直在制造的工厂
We have factories, which are like the factories you've been making which
使请求者功能，它们起到了方便的作用。
make requestor functions, they act as a convenience.
事实上，我向你们展示的四个功能都是工厂和
And in fact the four functions that I've shown you are all factories and
那么取消的取消函数可以由请求者返回以取消或
then cancel functions that cancel can be returned by a requestor to cancel or
请求。
request.
回调函数接受两个参数，
A callback function takes two parameters,
成功参数和失败参数。
a success parameter and a failure parameters.
如果未定义成功，则它失败，并且
If success is undefined then it fails and
失败是未定义的，当它成功时，只有一个回调
the failure is undefined when it succeeds and there's just one callback in
例如，承诺将有两个回调，一个用于成功，一个用于失败。
promises for example will be two callbacks one for success, one for failure.
我想如果你只有一个会更容易。
I think it's easier if you just have one.
然后请求者函数将接受回调，并且它还可以可选地采取
Than a requester function will take a call back and it can optionally also take
一个值，这就是序列如何将结果从一个步骤移动到下一个步骤。
a value and that's how a sequence will move results from one step to the next.
请求者函数可以返回Cancel函数，该函数用于
A requestor function can return a cancel function which is used for
取消和工厂提出请求。
cancellation and factories make requestors.
这就是四种函数的关系。
That's the relationship of the four kinds of functions.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：让我们看一个例子。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Let's look at an example.
这是身份请求者这是最简单的请求者
This is the identity requestor this is the simplest possible requestor It will
接收一个值，然后它会将该值发送到序列中的下一个对象。
receive a value and it will then send the value to the next thing in the sequence.
如果你把这个放在序列的中间，那就是什么都不做
If you put this in the middle of a sequence, it's a do nothing it
会把发生的一切都交给下一个。
will just take whatever's going on and give it to the next one.
你永远不会这样做，但这是最简单形式的模型。
You never do that but this is the model for the simplest form.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：我们可以包装这些东西，或者，对不起，这是全名请求
&gt;&gt; Douglas: We can wrap those things or, I'm sorry, this is the fullname request
这个接收包含部分名称的对象，我们将连接
this one receives an object containing parts of names and we'll concatenate
他们一起创建一个名字，然后将其传递给回调。
them together to make a name and then deliver that to the callback.
例如，我可以将此添加为处理步骤。
I could add this as a processing step for example.
我们可以编写一些函数来实现自动化
And we can write functions which will automate that for
我们，所以请求出现类似于您一直在编写的函数。
us, so request arise is similar to functions that you've been writing.
它将产生一个将调用一些普通函数的请求者。
It will produce a requestor that will call some ordinary function.
我们可以获取任何现有的函数，并将其转换为请求者，该请求者可以
We can take any existing function and turn it into a requestor which could
减少你在过渡到RQ时必须做的工作量。
reduce the amount of work you have to do in transiting to RQ.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：这是一个延迟请求者。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: This is a Delay Requestor.
这是最简单的实时事件。
This is the simplest real time thing.
您永远不会将延迟放入服务器应用程序中。
You would never put a delay into a server application.
在实际情况下，您将做的不是调用setTimeout，而是
What you would do in a real situation is instead of calling setTimeout, you're
将向某个服务发送消息，而不是调用clearTimeout
going to send a message to some service and instead of calling clearTimeout
您可能会向相同的服务发送一条消息，告诉它请停止。
you would send a message probably to the same service telling it to please stop.
您只需进行替换，但如果您要接受延迟请求者和
You just make the substitution but if you were to take the delay requestor and
把它放在一个序列中，这个序列将运行与它刚刚需要的完全相同
put it in a sequence, the sequence will run exactly the same it will just take
更长，但它将需要更长的时间没有阻塞。
longer but it will take longer without blocking.
如果是的话，这就是延迟工厂。
If then this is the Delay Factory.
这个代码是延迟请求者，除了
It's this code is the delay requestor except
工厂正在提供毫秒值。
the factory is providing the milliseconds value.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：这些都是RQ的一部分吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: These are all part of RQ?
&gt；&gt；Douglas：不，这些是你如何使用RQ的例子。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: No these are examples of how you could use RQ.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你放进去的东西没问题。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Things that you put in there okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：现在知道这个代码是。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Now know that this code is.
&gt；&gt；[CROSSTALK]&gt；&gt；Douglas：请求。
&gt;&gt; [CROSSTALK] &gt;&gt; Douglas: Request.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：那么这是一个读取文件的工厂。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Then this is a factory for reading files.
这个工厂将产生一个请求者，然后你可以
This factory will produce a requestor which you can then
放入一个列表，然后该列表将为您读取文件并
put in a list which will then read files for you and
这一个正在包装节点文件系统。
this one is wrapping the node file system.
这是我之前展示给你的演示中的小部件。
This is the widget that was in the demo that I showed you earlier.
这都是HTML垃圾，所以我不想用它来打扰你，但是
This is all HTML crap, so I'm not gonna bother you with that but
我这样做是因为我不想依赖任何人
and I did it this way cause I didn't want to have to depend on any one
图书馆，因为如果我选择了一个不是每个人都喜欢的图书馆，而且
library because if I chose a library that's not everybody's favorite, and
原来并不是每个人都是某人的最爱，所以
it turns out everybody is not somebody's favorite so
它只是，所以它是可怕的。
it's just, so it's awful.
但这里有趣的功能是，这是一个快速处理程序或
But the interesting features here are that this is the quick handler or
成功处理程序，所以当我在成功上点击是时，
the success handler, so when I clicked on yes on success,
我将小部件的颜色更改为绿色
I'd changed the color of the widget to green and
我调用了回调，让它知道它已成功完成，并且
I called the callback to let it know that it finished successfully and
在失败方面是相似的，除了我将背景颜色设置为粉红色和
on the failure side was similar except I set the background color to pink and
现在未定义成功，以指示我们有失败的结果和
success is undefined now to indicate that we have a failure result and
在取消的情况下，我只是将背景设置为灰色。
in the case of cancellation, I just set the background to gray.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：为什么要逆转你的成功填充者信念节点？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Why'd you reverse your success fillers conviction node?
&gt；&gt；Douglas：因为节点弄错了。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Because node got it wrong.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：因为它弄错了吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Because it got it wrong?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay,
我同意这看起来真的很奇怪，但是
I agree that it seemed really weird but
现在你开始用雇佣的人来做正确的事情，这看起来很奇怪。
now you start to use to hire people who do it the right way it seems weird.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：是的，没错，我知道我在危险中提到过这一点，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, exactly and I know I mentioned this in the hazard,
在一个做错事的系统中做正确的事情。
doing things right in a system that does things wrong.
&gt；&gt；[笑]&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，而且
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas: It's going to, yeah, and
我明白。
I understand that.
我为此道歉。
I apologize for it.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：我就是不能让自己
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay. &gt;&gt; Douglas: I just couldn't bring myself
用错误的方式去做。
to do it the wrong way.